<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>flbrack.com</title>
    <link>https://flbrack.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on flbrack.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Fionn Bracken</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://flbrack.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Break The Web</title>
      <link>https://flbrack.com/posts/2023-02-15-dont-break-the-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flbrack.com/posts/2023-02-15-dont-break-the-web/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t Break The Web As a web developer, I like to follow prominent people working in the web on twitter. It was there that I came across this exchange between Rich Harris, the creator of the web framework Svelte, and Jarred Sumner, the creator of the new javascript runtime Bun.
Smooshgate?
As much as I think people should have their own website, this exchange does highlight some of what&amp;rsquo;s great about social media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agent Based Disease Modelling - Interactive Intro</title>
      <link>https://flbrack.com/posts/2021-07-01-agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flbrack.com/posts/2021-07-01-agent/</guid>
      <description>My Masters Project: An Interactive Introduction As part of my Masters coursework I must complete a Summer project. Partly inspired by the recent events in the world, I have chosen to do my project on Agent Based Disease Modelling.
Traditional Modelling Methods Modern mathematical modelling is a rich subject, which informs a huge part of our lives, from weather forecasts, to bookies&amp;rsquo; prices, to public health advice. Disease modelling is of course one area that has been in the news a great deal lately, for obvious reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a Website with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://flbrack.com/posts/2021-06-28-built-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flbrack.com/posts/2021-06-28-built-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>How I Made This Website Everyone Should Have a Website Everyone should have their own website. In the early days of the of the internet, a much higher percentage of internet users had their own webpage. As the internet opened up to less tech-savvy people, social media websites became the places where people would share their thoughts. This is for good reason, humans are social animals and social media allowed for much greater interaction and social networking than personal webpages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://flbrack.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flbrack.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Fionn Bracken and this is my website.
I live in Ireland and I currently work as a software engineer, mostly as a web developer. I studied maths in college, and enjoy coding and chess, but I&amp;rsquo;m not as nerdy as that sounds (I hope).
Some non-nerdy interests are swimming, cycling and supporting my local music scene and my local football team Cork City FC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
